match4jobs.com 2009-04-26

# Match4jobs - Homepage

Privacy Statement

This website is managed by Match4Jobs as described below. Match4Jobs is meticulous in regards to protecting our users' privacy. Our aim is to provide users with a secure user environment. The intention of this policy is to inform you -as user- of the way we will use the personal information supplied by users on this website. It is not applicable to data that has been gathered any other way. This policy is applicable to jobseekers and employers.   
Match4Jobs works in accordance with the protection of privacy legislation. This legislation regulates the processing of information relating to you and from it you derive several rights regarding your personal data.   
Our sites contain links to other websites, which we do not control. Match4Jobs is not responsible for the policies or practices of those other websites, whose links you can click on this site. We recommend that you read said sites' privacy policies, to get an idea of how they gather, use and share information regarding their users.   
This Privacy statement is solely applicable to the information we gather via this website and is not applicable to information we gather in any other way.   
  
Gathering and storing information **  
**  
You do not need to supply us with personal information in order to search for jobs on our site. If and when you wish to register with Match4Jobs (in order to receive newsletters and vacancies by e-mail) we may however ask you to submit personal details like name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, where to contact you, billing information, CV and other information which will reveal your identity. We will use your personal details and other information you provide in accordance with this privacy statement. Note that, as long as you provide us with a working e-mail address where we can contact you, you have the option to leave out those personal details and limit the CV and information provided to a description of your background and interests, which we require to provide you with our services, i.e. find jobs that match your background and interests. If you leave out your personal details, we may still disclose your CV and other information you provided us with to third parties according to the paragraphs 'Building and uploading a CV' and 'Disclosing information to third parties' below, except for your email address.

There may be other parts of the Match4Jobs website where we ask you for personal information. Certain areas of the Match4Jobs site may be used to gather demographical data that are not uniquely applicable to you like postal code, age, sex and the kind of work that interests you. In some cases we may collect a combination of these two different kinds of information which may then be combined with information derived from other Match4Jobs sources. We make use of cookies and other forms of technology to gather an impression of your activities within our websites in order to be able to offer you optimal, made-to-measure service. We have informed the College Bescherming Persoonsgegevens (CBP), the Dutch body governing the protection of privacy of personal information, of our activities. Your information will be safely stored on a server in the Netherlands   
  
Match4Jobs' use of your information  
  
When you supply your personal information you give express permission for your personal details to be used for the following purposes:   

  *  We use your personal information, gathered from our website, including any demographical, collective and technical data in the execution and control of your registration with Match4Jobs, to answer any questions you might have, to operate and improve the website, to promote a positive user environment and in order to provide the products and services we offer to jobseekers and employers; 
  * We may use your personal details in order to be able to inform you of other products or services offered by Match4Jobs and its partners; 
  * We may share information about your background and interests, including any personal details you choose to provide us, to Match4Jobs' clients who may then be able to get in touch with you regarding a particular vacancy; 
  * Your personal details may be used to inform you of relevant vacancies suitable to your profile; 
  * We may also use your contact details to send you information on other work-related products and services on offer; 
  * Should you not wish your details to be used for this you may use the Match4Jobs contactform  to let us know. 

Building and uploading a CV  
  
As the Match4Jobs website, part of Match4Jobs, is a site to promote your career, we offer the option of adding your CV to our database. There are two ways of doing this:   
1\. You may save your CV in our database by uploading it (function: Upload My CV )   
2\. You may use the CV builder.   
If you choose to use this option, you give express permission for your CV and the personal information it contains, to be consulted by and/or distributed to employers, recruitment consultants and any others that have paid a fee to have access to our database or to obtain a copy of said database   
Should you not wish your CV to be accessible to us or third parties, please remove your account or contact us on [info@match4jobs.com](mailto:info@match4jobs.com). We are making every effort to limit access to our searchable CV databases (or copies thereof) to paying employers, recruitment consultants, recruitment managers, head hunters and Human Resource officers, and to reserve them for law enforcement and national security agencies, but we cannot guarantee that other parties will not be able to obtain access to our database.   
We will not be held liable for the use made of the CVs by third parties that have obtained access to said CVs whilst stored in our searchable database. You may remove your CV from our searchable database at any time, following the steps set out below. However, it may still be possible for employers, recruitment consultants or others that have paid access to our database, or a copy thereof, as well as for parties having obtained access to the database by other means, to have saved a copy of your CV in their personal files or databases. We are not liable for the storage, the use and/or the privacy of CVs or profiles in this event.   
Should you supply us with references, it will be your responsibility to ensure that this person is aware of his/her personal details having been forwarded, and having granted you written permission to do so. 

We strongly recommend that your CV does not contain any information regarding your   
I. race or ethnicity;   
II. political opinions;   
III. philosophical or religious convictions;   
IV. membership of trade unions or political parties;   
V. physical or mental health;   
VI. sexual orientation;   
VII. police records or involvement in legal procedures.   
Should your CV contain this kind of information, please remember that you have given permission for us to store and use this information in accordance with this Statement. 

Disclosing information to third parties  
  
We will not disclose personal details, combined personal and demographical details pertaining to you or your use of the website (such as the parts of the site that you visit or the services you have access to) to third parties, barring the following circumstances:   
1\. We may disclose said details to third parties if and when you have uploaded a CV or have used the CV builder. If and when you avail yourself of those services it constitutes automatic agreement. See our terms and conditions. Should you use any of said services, all parties that have access to our searchable database (or copies thereof) will have access to it. You may render your CV not-accessible at any time by removing your account or having it removed.   
2\. We may disclose this information to companies and those in our employ that act on our behalf, including data operators and companies and/or individual resident outside the European Economic Area. Activities carried out on our behalf comprise hosting our web servers, analysing data, rendering assistance in marketing and offering customer support. Said companies and/or individuals will have access to your personal details insofar as is necessary fort them to carry out their work. They may not however share this information with other third parties or use said information for any other purpose. We will be in control of and responsible for any and all data that are shared in this manner.   
3\. We may disclose personal information if and when the law demands, or we are requested to do so by government and/or legal agencies, or if we -in good faith- consider this to be necessary in order:   
a. to comply with legislation or a legal summons;   
b. to protect the rights and/or property of Match4Jobs or affiliated companies;   
c. to prevent criminal action or to safeguard national security;   
d. to safeguard the personal security of either the users or the general public.   
4\. We may disclose said information and hand it over to any third party that has obtained control of all or of a significant part of Match4Jobs, regardless of whether this acquisition has occurred by means of a merger or purchase of all, or of a significant part of, our assets. Moreover, should Match4Jobs -voluntarily or involuntarily- be involved in receivership and/or bankruptcy proceedings, Match4Jobs, her administrator or (official) receiver may sell, license, or otherwise dispose of these data in a legally approved transaction. Should any of this occur, we will inform you of the sale of all, or a significant part, of our company to a third party, either by e-mail or by means of a clearly visible announcement on the Match4Jobs website.
